



# **Profile**

I have been dealing with various software for about 10 years. In my early years I was involved with **CMS** systems (**Opencart**, **WordPress** etc). I have been working as a Frontend Developer with **JavaScript**, **ReactJS** (Redux), **NodeJS**, **HTML**, **CSS** and **MongoDB** for about 2 years.

# Employment History

#### Front-End Developer at Freelance, Istanbul

2018 - Present

- I have been working in the e-commerce industry for 4 years
- I know the problems or the sector and produce solutions to these problems.
- Mastered e-commerce terminology by working in the field
- Systems I used throughout the process: Wordpress, Opencart and basic javascript, html and css

# Front-End Developer (Intern) at ETurnsoft, Turkey

2022 - 2022

- Working on User Management System with admin panel.
- Using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, ReactJs, NodeJs, Bootstrap, and MongoDB



# Education

**Depertman of Economics at Karadeniz Teknical University, Trabzon** 2010 - 2014

Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp (with Agile Tegnology ), SoftInnovas Bootcamp, Istanbul

2021 - 2022



# Courses

Full-Stack Javascript Development at SoftInnovas, Istanbul 2021 - 2022

# **Details**

Istanbul, Turkey +905301142548 halit.uzan@gmail.com

## Links

Github : @halituzan Linkedin : @halituzan

Portfolio: halituzan.github.io

# Skills

Javascript
HTML
CSS
ReactJs
NodeJs
MongoDB
Bootstrap
Tailwindcss
Git
Opencart
Wordpress
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop

# Languages

English (A2)

## **Hobbies**

Camping, Fishing, Traveling, Flowers and Plants